/** @type {import('sequelize-cli').Migration} */
module.exports = {
  async up(queryInterface, Sequelize) {
    await queryInterface.bulkInsert('Cards', [{
      question: 'Meat',
      answer: 'Мясо',
      topicId: 1,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    }, {
      question: 'Carrot',
      answer: 'Морковь',
      topicId: 1,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Egg',
      answer: 'Яйцо',
      topicId: 1,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Cucumber',
      answer: 'Огурец',
      topicId: 1,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Pie',
      answer: 'Пирог',
      topicId: 1,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Garlic',
      answer: 'Чеснок',
      topicId: 1,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Plane',
      answer: 'Самолет',
      topicId: 2,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Luggage',
      answer: 'Багаж',
      topicId: 2,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Vacation',
      answer: 'Отпуск',
      topicId: 2,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Sightseeing',
      answer: 'Осмотр достопримечательностей',
      topicId: 2,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Foreigner',
      answer: 'Иностранец',
      topicId: 2,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Language',
      answer: 'Язык',
      topicId: 2,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Raccoon',
      answer: 'Енот',
      topicId: 3,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    }, {
      question: 'Lion',
      answer: 'Лев',
      topicId: 3,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Cat',
      answer: 'Кот',
      topicId: 3,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Squarrel',
      answer: 'Белка',
      topicId: 3,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Turtle',
      answer: 'Черепаха',
      topicId: 3,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    {
      question: 'Dolphin',
      answer: 'Дельфин',
      topicId: 3,
      createdAt: new Date(),
      updatedAt: new Date(),
    },
    ]);
  },
  async down(queryInterface, Sequelize) {
    await queryInterface.bulkDelete('Cards', null, {});
  },
};
